Fore!
Foreign! Foreign!
foreignch.
[Music]
ForeN.com.
All right, at the count of three, two,
one, prize is here with us.
Congratulations. Let's take a few
pictures.
>> 3
2 1
[Music]
[Applause]
And with that, ladies and gentlemen, CAS
Satia is now officially launched with
the migrations plan that's already
protecting over 20,000 lives and
counting. Thanks to our partnership,
Bank Simmon National, we share our
commitment to transforming how Malaysian
Asian landscape in Malaysia. And at WB,
we had a very simple vision, changing
the way how people feel about Asian. We
believe Asian should not be intimidating
or inaccessible. Instead, it should be a
source of empowerment, a safety net, and
a fundamental right for everyone.
Cases reflects our unwavering commitment
to making insurance to assessment for
all. It's more than just a micro
insurance. It's a meaningful step
towards empowering underserved community
giving them the protection and
confidence they deserve. This is not
just about migration. It's about
financial inclusion and literacy. is
about breaking down the barriers and
ensuring that protection is not a luxury
reserve for the field but reasonable
accessible to all Malaysian while also
equip them with the knowledge to make
informal financial choices. We are also
grateful to our partnership with Bank
Siman National. Their extensive network
and deep understanding of Malaysian
community allow us to extend the reach
of gases here, enabling us to deliver
meaningful protection to those who need
the most in line with the vision on no
Malaysian left behind.
Certia is designed to provide a
affordable protection with a hassle-free
and easy to understand allowing
individual and family to face the future
with greater confidence. I'm to announce
since it launched in April 2025 just a
few months ago, Kas sur has already
covered more than 20,000 lives
demonstrating the critical need for this
type of Asian product. Our dedicated ESG
is also evident in our proactive efforts
to build a stronger communities to
initiative like Casia which provide
affordable accessible solution directly
addressing the need of underserved
population in Malaysia to boost
awareness understanding of CAD. We are
having a road show a beautiful place
over here in conjunction with FWD Fiesta
Kim 2025. This exciting initiative will
not only showcase the product benefit
and how it protect family but also
giving all the part to try to win the
gravite of brand new port X50.
One of the highlight of this road show
is to engage and educate the public
about the important the importance of
financial planning and the role can play
in achieving financial security and
peace of mind. Let's work hand in hand
together to make financial literacy and
empowerment ready for everyone. This is
our goal and we at FW are fully
committed to make it happen together
with your partner PSN. Thank you very
much.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, let's give a big
round of applause to Mr. Mark. Thank you
so much.
Um but this is to combine what FWD
uh feel about changing the way people
feel about insurance and if you combine
that with our vision BSN vision of no
Malaysian left behind it is actually a
very powerful statement right first is
to to feel differently about how
insurance should be uh covered to all
walks of life and our vision of no
Malaysian left behind uh and you Not
very long ago, people used to say, "What
is so difficult about financial
inclusion?" Um, but I bet, you know,
Mark, you've been with us with this uh
journey of empowering microinsurers,
making sure everyone is uh able to be
protected.
Um, it does require a lot of innovation.
uh it does require a lot of innovation
from a product perspective so that we
can continue this journey of ensuring no
Malaysian left behind and changing the
way how people feel about insurance. So
I think that's a very very tacky uh
cheeky tagline that we can use. I'm not
sure if that would enable me to win the
X50. Uh but that's that's a very
powerful statement and I think this is
something that we would like to come and
celebrate. uh thanking our partner FWD
for always making sure that we are hit
in in terms of innovating products so
that we can continue to uh empower lives
uh making sure people are protected in
every way and more importantly is to
make sure we are able to um ensure no
Malaysians are left behind. I mean you
you quoted some very good stats about
how 20 cents a day
um you know it's it's nicer to say 20
cents a day than to say 70 ringgit perm.
Uh but 20 cents a day gives you the
opportunity for protection up to 90,000
of um of accidental death and 15,000 I'm
trying to recall so that I say the right
things. uh 15,000 for non-acal and TPD.
So, you know, with just 20 cents a day.
On top of that, you have the 3,000
funeral expenses. Nothing to do with
protection there, but it it helps it
helps when it comes to the time of
needs. Uh so these are things that we do
uh together PSN and FWD and we are very
happy to partner
um our very um orange outfit uh uh you
know very vibrant partner to bring about
this innovation so that we can continue
to nurture and make sure people are
protected in every way uh and also the
journey of no Malaysian left behind.
Um now you know we we actually launched
this in April and the uptake has been um
uh has been very encouraging. We have um
you know easily insured more than 20,000
lives. Uh and together with our casia
bakti which we launched last year we
have covered almost 180,000 lives. So
that that's those are significant
milestone that we would like to
celebrate today. uh and also to launch a
product that we feel uh will continue to
uh to nurture lives. Uh so those are
very powerful statement um in line with
bankara's
pindong program uh and also the national
financial inclusion framework uh which
is both very important. First is the way
you feel about insurance. Second is
about uh making sure no Malaysian left
behind. Um and you know at BSN we go
beyond excess. Um we integrate financial
literacy into our approach. Uh
empowering nations to make informed
decisions. Uh to recognize their
opinions to weigh their priorities and
to act with a lot of confidence.
uh and this is how we ensure every
individual can build last sorry lasting
financial security and resilience in all
that in all that makes um in one word if
I could summarize that it's actually
innovation so thank you for continuing
this innovation journey um so as you
explore this uh road show uh talk to our
team talk to the team from FWD
um they are very easily identified uh
the ones uh in orange jumpers including
you, Shik. You better make sure you have
enough product knowledge on FWD. Uh
that's the criteria for you to come back
on stage the the next round. Um and also
to discover how uh a lot of our
solutions uh from micro financing to go
savings uh can help secure your future.
Uh my very big thanks again uh and
gratitude to Mark. Uh you know iPhone is
here, Sean is here. Sean has decided to
sit on BSN side today uh because he
feels very connected to us uh in driving
innovation and also hearing what we
because when we go down to the ground um
a lot of times we we know we hear
grieviances we hear grouses and this is
really getting connected uh right to the
core and making sure that we have
solution that we can bring back to them.
Uh and Sean has been very very helpful.
Uh together with my team here, Chip
Mujib, uh FISA is also here. Uh AA who's
been driving the numbers. Uh you know,
the folks at the back. Um they are the
actual workers. Uh we are just here to
you know, ha hoha. Hello. Uh so thank
thank you to thank you. Thank you so
much to the team and everyone who has
make this a success. Thank you so much.